http://www.federal-bank.com/privacy-policy

Navigation
Skip to Content
BE UPDATED
Get the latest updates from www.federalbank.co.in through website notifications
Fed-e-Trade
National Pension System (NPS)
Immediate Payment Service
Electronic Clearing Service (ECS)
PayLite
Pay Fees & Bills+
Telephone Bill Payment (Fed-e-Pay)
Visa Bill Pay
NETC (National Electronic Toll Collection)
Tele Banking
NETC (National Electronic Toll Collection)
Portfolio Investment Scheme
National Pension System (NPS)
Pay Fees & Bills+
Telephone Bill Payment (Fed-e-Pay)
Packing Credit Limit
Packing Credit Loan in Foreign Currency (PCFC)
Rediscounting of Export Bills Abroad(EBRD)
Anywhere Banking
Electronic Clearing Service (ECS)
Easy Payments
Telephone Bill Payment (Fed-e-Pay)
Privacy Policy
At Federal Bank our principal concern is the responsible use of information that users and clients share and disclose to us. Federal Bank's commitment towards guaranteed confidentiality and privacy at all times is clearly articulated in our Privacy Policy. We will use our best efforts to ensure that the information you submit to us remains private, and is used only for the purpose for which it is submitted.
This Policy holds true for a non-customer who has provided information to the Bank by any means, with or without the intentions of establishing a relationship, of whatsoever nature, with the Bank. By divulging any information to us, users agree to the terms and conditions of this Policy.
Collecting Customer / Personal Information
We collect information that users provide voluntarily to us . Except for the purposes and under the circumstances mentioned in this Policy, Federal Bank does not provide any information of users to a third party without specifically informing the users at the time of collection or without the express consent of users themselves.
Use of Access Log Files
Federal Bank logs IP addresses, browser type, number of pages viewed etc. in order to provide better service for our users. We use the information to get page view statistics, to analyze trends and better understand the usage of the site, and for system administration purposes.
Use of User Information
Federal Bank may use the Customer Information for the purposes , inter –alia , customer identification/ verification, providing of financial services and products, for customization of products or services, marketing or promotion of financial products/ services; to check credit rating, enforcement of Customer obligations and such other purpose to facilitate optimal and high quality services.
Federal Bank reserves the right to perform statistical analysis of user behaviours and preferences in order to measure users' relative interests in the various areas of the web site for the purpose of product and service development. The analysis is anonymous and not tagged to identifiable users. The analytical data that Federal Bank collects is for internal use only to improve the content and services of its web site. In return, users will benefit from improved quality of services.
Disclosure to Third Parties
Unless Federal Bank specifically informs users at the time of collection, or unless users give express consent, Federal Bank does not provide any personally identifying information to a third party. However, if permitted or required by law or subpoenaed or ordered by a court of law or to enforce the Terms and Conditions of the Products or services or to safeguard / defend our rights , interests and properties or that of our affiliates , Federal Bank will have to disclose to the proper authorities the personal information of any individual user.
Federal Bank may disclose the data created after statistical analysis (not tagged to identifiable users) to any person, without any limitation and the User hereby give your consent for the same. Federal Bank may disclose Customer Information to any of the Federal Bank’s associates and affiliates, without any limitation and the User / Client hereby give consent for the same.
We may disclose the Customer Information to third parties for purposes, inter alia, for advertising, for any joint product promotion campaigns or for availing support services, for participation in electronic clearing network etc. .
We may also share with third parties, the information obtained with your consent, from your mobile device like device location, device information (including storage, model, installed apps, Wi-Fi , mobile network etc. ), transactional and promotional SMS , communication and call logs, for purposes including statistical analysis, credit rating etc. in order to enable us to provide you banking / financial services with high quality and standards. However, while disclosing any such information to third parties as afore-mentioned, we will make reasonable efforts to bind them with obligation to keep the same secure and confidential and an obligation to use the information for the purpose for which the same is disclosed, and you hereby give your consent for the same.
Links to Other Materials
Linked sites are not under the control of Federal Bank, and Federal Bank will not be held responsible for the content or privacy policies of any linked sites or any links containing other linked sites.
Updating of Privacy Policy and Consent
Federal Bank will, as and when it deems fit to do so, change, alter or modify its Privacy Policy. Users are advised to visit the site continually in order to monitor changes in the policy, as the policy will be binding upon them in relation to their use of Federal Bank 's services.
Use of SMS for Registration/Activation of Mobile Apps/Online Channels
Federal Bank uses SMS /OTP based procedure for activation of its official mobile applications & online platforms for security reasons & system administration purposes. We do not publicly disclose any personal or sensitive user data related to financial or payment activities or any government identification numbers to any third party, except in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy.
Security
We have taken reasonable measures to protect security and confidentiality of the Customer Information and its transmission through the World Wide Web. You are required to follow the Terms and Conditions while using this Website including the instructions stated therein in respect of security and confidentiality of your Log-in and Password.
The Bank will give access to Customer Information to only authorised employees. Employees who violate this Privacy Policy shall be subject to disciplinary process as per the byelaws of the Bank. Any employee who withdraws from the employment of the Bank will have to undertake to abide by this Privacy Policy and keep all Customer Information secure and confidential.
Locate Us
Login
Interest Rates
Priority Banking
Locate us
Branches & ATMs
+
Overseas Representatives
+
Corporate Mobile Banking FedCorp (Web)
+
Easy Payments
+
PayLite Portal
+
Interest Rates
Interest rate for Deposits
+
+
Did you know that your internet Explorer is out of date ?
To get best possoble experience using our site we recommend that you upgrade to a newer version of Internet Explorer or choose another web browser. A list of the most popular web browsers can be found below.
Google Chrome
Mozilla Firefox
Internet Explorer 10+
Opera
Safari (Mac & IOS)
